{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Allosteric enzymes are", "opta": "larger than simple enzyme", "optb": "smaller than simple enzyme", "optc": "larger and more complex than simple enzyme", "optd": "smaller than simple enzyme but not complex", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Intracellular enzymes", "opta": "synthesize cellular material only", "optb": "synthesize cellular material and perform catabolic reaction", "optc": "synthesize cellular material and perform anabolic reaction", "optd": "only provide energy to the cell", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Enzyme catalase has non-protein metal as", "opta": "magnesium", "optb": "manganese", "optc": "iron", "optd": "zinc", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Isozymes or iso enzymes are those enzyme which", "opta": "have same structural forms", "optb": "have different structural forms but identical catalytic properties", "optc": "catalyses oxidation reactions", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Enzymes are", "opta": "organic compounds produced by living organism", "optb": "inorganic compounds", "optc": "organic as well as inorganic compounds", "optd": "all of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Main function of an enzyme is to", "opta": "increase the activation energy", "optb": "decrease the activation energy", "optc": "maintain constant activation energy", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Who coined the word enzyme first?", "opta": "Kuhne", "optb": "Pasteur", "optc": "Liebig", "optd": "Buchner", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The inactive protein from of enzyme is", "opta": "apoenzyme", "optb": "enzyme", "optc": "haloenzyme", "optd": "cofactor", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The inactive organic molecular portion of enzyme is", "opta": "apoenzyme", "optb": "coenzyme", "optc": "holoenzyme", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Many enzymes consists of a protein combined with low molecular weight organic molecule called as", "opta": "apoenzyme", "optb": "co-enzyme", "optc": "holoenzyme", "optd": "co-factors", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Organic molecules that increase the rate of metabolic reactions with themselves changing are known as", "opta": "coenzymes", "optb": "enzymes", "optc": "substrates", "optd": "reactants", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Protein portion of an enzyme when it is combined with organic molecule is termed as", "opta": "apoenzyme", "optb": "co-enzyme", "optc": "holoenzyme", "optd": "co-factors", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The active form of enzyme is", "opta": "apoenzyme", "optb": "coenzyme", "optc": "holoenzyme", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Enzymes can", "opta": "not pass through semipermeable membrane", "optb": "pass through semipermeable membrane", "optc": "dissolve semipermeable membrane", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}